MARLON JOSÉ DA VEIGA SANTOS

Not married

Born in 28/04/1988 in São Paulo, Brazil

Address: Rua Pedro Fernandes Aragão – 04431-160 Phone numbers: (11)5611-0023 / (11)96444-1033

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/marlon-veiga-santos

Github: https://github.com/marlonveiga-santos

Blog: https://bemcodar.wordpress.com

Objective Overview

I am seeking internship vacancies, aiming areas like cloud and data-science. Also seeking for job as an analyst or system developer.

Technical Skills

- Knowledge in front-end: HTML5, CSS3, Java Script (JS4 and ES 2015)
- Knowledge in back-end: PHP, JSP, Apache and Node JS.
- Knowledge in cloud: Azure, IBM Cloud, Docker.
- Knowledge in languages: C++, Java, Java script, SQL, Python, VBA.
- Knowledge in systems: Windows (advanced) and Linux (Basic skills)
- Miscellaneous knowledge: Office 365, Jupyter notebooks, IBM Watson, Visual Studio Code, Netbeans, Gcc, VNC, Github, CMD/Bash.

Personal Skills / languages

Local and remote end user support. Preparation of manuals in Portuguese and English, maintenance of printers, preparation of rooms for presentations. Technical presentations.

English intermediate: advanced reading and writing and basic conversation. Considered proficient by the Paula Sousa Center.

Team spirit, sense of urgency, sense of ownership, self-taught. I intend in a space of 5 years to become a reference in the diffusion of knowledge on cloud and data-science in Brazil.

Hobbies, karaoke, emulators, reading and walking.

Education

FATEC Zona Sul

Systems Analysis and Development - 2017 – studying.

E. E. México

high school - 2006-2008.

Work Experience

Answerdesk Microsoft - Teleperformance - R\$ 1.600,00 - 08/2015 (atual)

- Official Microsoft support in Brazil for home users. Dominate the Windows and Office environment in their versions from Office 2007 and Windows 7 until current versions.

IT and infrastructure analyst Jr. Nec - R\$ 1.300,00 - 02/2014 à 11/2014

- Responsible for IT support and direct telephony. Asset relocation and cabling. Answering calls with SLA.

Electronic technician Jr. - ADT Security Services - R\$ 700,00 - 03/2009 a 02/2011

- Installation of residential and commercial security systems. Execution of infrastructure works and training. Acting and contact with clients in situations of fragility due to thefts.

Note: I have more performances, but I emphasize the ones that got the most learning.